<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sully Squared</title><link>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sully Squared</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 22:22:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why most QA Automation Fails</title><link>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/05-15-2021-qa-automation-fails/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 22:22:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/05-15-2021-qa-automation-fails/</guid><description>Overview Recently, I made a poll on what would be my next blog post topic, and a lot of my network is interested in what I view as major reasons that most QA Automation endeavors fail:
Given that I spent a significant amount of my time in my early career doing SDET work, as well as beginning to develop an understanding the benefit of having a DevOps based culture within IT organizations, this post will discuss my conclusions as to what I feel makes for a failed automation effort.</description></item><item><title>How I embed Saucelab Build Videos into Azure Pipelines</title><link>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/04-06-2021-saucelabs-azure-pipelines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 13:16:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/04-06-2021-saucelabs-azure-pipelines/</guid><description>Overview of Saucelabs For those of you that don&amp;rsquo;t know, within the QA Automation world there are many tools in which we can leverage to distribute and run our Selenium tests on. One popular tool that I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the market is Saucelabs. While it is entirely possible to utilize your CI job&amp;rsquo;s resources to run these tests, one thing that made using Saucelabs very appealing to me was the ability to actually view video playback of your test in action.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to my Blog</title><link>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/04-05-2021-welcome-to-my-blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 17:57:48 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ssulei7.github.io/posts/04-05-2021-welcome-to-my-blog/</guid><description>About me Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Sully, and welcome to my blog! I am a DevOps Engineer with a former background in software engineering and academia. I am well known for my iconic salmon blazer:
Purpose of my Blog The purpose of this blog is to share my overall journey as to how I got to where I am right now, as well as share some of the things that I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on.</description></item></channel></rss>